Scarlett's disappeared.
It's been two days
since I've seen His Lordship.
I thought she went away because
she exhausted herself back then,
but now I'm sure I was wrong.
Did she get "fed up" with me, as they say?
Constance Grail. You have a visitor.
You ungrateful girl.
Think about what you've put me through.
One day, out of the blue,
I hear my daughter's been arrested,
so I rush back to the capital
only to find her slated for execution.
I... I'm sorry.
What on earth is going on?
Father...
Please disown me.
What if blame were to spread
to our family because of me?
I don't know much about palace intrigue.
I don't know what's happening
in this country, either.
But...
I think I can at least take a stand
to keep my daughter safe.
But consider the risks!
Listen, Constance.
Nothing inspires us like other people,
no matter the era.
We have our own ways of doing things.
"Be you sincere."
I'm glad to see you looking well.
Here you go.
Thanks!
What do you want with me, Shoshanna?
Change the people keeping watch.
Why?
They get rough.
Who knows what they'll do
if someone stands up to them?
So be it.
Kiriki kirikuku.
L-Lie low and stay calm.
Kindly withdraw.
What do you want with us?
I came to warn you, brave little lady.
Unless you want to die,
keep your head down.
You're awfully kind.
Kind?
Yes. You and Shoshanna both.
I'll kill you if ordered to do so.
I know. And that's why you came, isn't it?
To make sure you won't get that order.
To make sure I'm not killed.
I don't believe it!
Connie, kidnap a prince of Faris?!
And now she's to be publicly executed?!
Say, Mylene,
wasn't public execution abolished
after Scarlett Castiel?
Do you know why?
Yes. I believe a citizens'
group protested.
The Violet Association,
I think it was called.
The Violet Association?
Thank you, Mylene.
Huh? Where are you going?
To save Connie, of course.
You can't expect me
to just sit around weeping.
So I've got to take action!
My, what an admirable attitude.
Spare me your theatrics.
You've been able to see me
all along, haven't you?
I've no doubt you realized I was there
since we met at the Grand Merillian.
Otherwise, you'd never have bothered with
the engagement of a viscount's daughter.
I have an excellent memory.
Oh, how heartrending!
10 YEARS AGO
Might your humble servant
assist you in any way?
You're an eyesore. Get out of my sight.
Oh, what a shame.
Should the fancy ever strike you,
please call upon your humble servant.
Yes. If the fancy strikes.
It took ten years,
but the fancy struck me at last.
So...
lend me your aid.
In that case,
how may this unworthy hog be of service?
By hunting rats.
Your Royal Highness Prince Theophilis,
Kendall Levine of the
diplomatic service is here.
What? I thought he left
on a mission to Adelbide.
Regarding that,
he claims there's been
an urgent development.
Is that so?
Show him in.
It's been ages, Kendall.
What on earth is the matter?
With all due respect,
Prince Ulysses was abducted not
by Adelbide, but by Daeg Gallus,
and Second Prince Roderick
is in league with them.
What?
I'm told that every member of Daeg Gallus
bears a tattoo of the sun
somewhere on their bodies.
A tattoo?
I never suspected Roderick!
Where exactly did you
get this information?
From Third Princess Alexandra.
In the ordinary course of events,
I was to receive charity from
Prince Enrique in the near future.
Charity?
Indeed. To facilitate
spreading the divine word,
we need "contributions" from the faithful
more substantial than prayers.
I doubt that my brother
would do any such thing.
You must be mistaken.
You don't say.
Then pray forgive my intrusion.
By the way...
What is it?
Have you need of divine aid yourself,
Your Royal Highness?
Well, I...
Begging your pardon.
Am I interrupting?
No. The viscount was just leaving.
And you are...?
Rufus May.
I was recently appointed
assistant comptroller of the treasury.
Why, then you're the man
I've heard about!
Have you ever visited my church?
I'm afraid not, as I'm still new
to my post. But someday.
Why, we would be delighted to have you.
Oh, do forgive me.
Static electricity, I suppose.
That, or a whim of the goddesses.
Don't you feel pain?
Of course I do.
It's merely that any pain you inflict
is the greatest of joys to me.
Now, did anything strike you?
That man kept his gloves on,
even when you went to shake hands.
He has a sun tattoo on his wrist.
Rufus May is a rat.
Uncover his antecedents at once.
My lady's wish is my command.
Now then, I can do this much safely...
I always feel sleepy
after using that power.
I suppose I feel fine now
because I kept it weak earlier.
I see.
Causing such phenomena
consumes a great deal of energy.
How would you know about that?
For all my faults,
I do have the goddesses' favor.
By the way, is revenge your reason
for remaining in this world?
Of course it is.
Even now?
What are you getting at?
Here and now, are you
being driven by revenge?
Or...
are you working to save Constance Grail?
Revenge, naturally.
Is that so?
I believe that, to remain
in the world of the living,
a disembodied soul must have
some powerful emotion or goal.
So I have no doubt that once you feel
your revenge is complete,
you will return to the gods' side.
Please sign our petition
against this execution!
Constance Grail is innocent!
Please.
I beg you. Lend us your aid.
Please help us! We can't save
my friend Constance Grail
without assistance from
the right-minded people here!
What's the meaning of this?
I gave strict orders to keep
any petition out of the palace,
and not just commoners have signed this.
Aristocrats are in on it as well.
Then there's this book...
It claims to be by an up-and-coming
foreign author. Adam Hicks?
It's obviously Amelia Hobbes!
A viscount's daughter, lauded as a saint,
overcomes the gap in status
to marry a crown prince.
But in reality, she's a member
of a criminal syndicate
who was born an impoverished orphan.
I feel as though
I've heard this plot before.
Why would they go to such lengths
for that plain little girl?
No matter what anyone says,
she will be executed.
Along with that Lucia girl
the O'Brians adopted.
What is it?
Nothing.
What an unpleasant state of affairs.
And just look how those absurd rumors
spread when one's not looking.
What rumors?
Haven't you heard?
I mean about Constance Grail.
They say she can hear
the voices of the dead
and that she's working to clear
Scarlett Castiel's name.
Crown Princess Cecilia?!
They say you can speak with the dead.
W-Well...
Liar.
The dead don't talk.
They have no thoughts.
They just turn to ashes.
It's only natural.
At least, that's how it was for me.
I've never heard any voices.
Whose voice...
DID YOU WANT TO HEAR?
14 YEARS AGO
Cici!
Go give that back!
What? Why should I, Cess?
Picking pockets is a crime!
I'm not letting you lead a life
you can't be proud of
while I've got my eye on you!
Hey, mister!
You did it! That's my Cici!
Hey, quit it!
Cici, Cess! You're back!
Listen, there's this weird guy here.
Weird how?
He says he's looking
for a girl named Cecilia!
He's sure got his work
cut out for him, huh, Cess?
Yeah. There's loads of Cecilias,
even just at our place.
You there. You're called Cess?
Then is your real name Cecilia?
Y-Yes.
Your eyes...
look rosy in the right light, I suppose.
Sister, I'd like to have
a chat with this girl.
He said the lord's daughter was
born sickly and won't live much longer.
So I'm going to play
the part of Miss Cecilia.
Why you?
He said the lord had
a secret child with a whore.
Her name happened to be Cecilia too,
and they put her in some orphanage
right after she was born.
Couldn't he have the wrong girl?
I mean, that description would fit—
I don't think he cares
whether I'm the real one or not.
I just happen to fit the bill.
But that doesn't mean you have to...
He says the lord will donate
to the orphanage.
So you'll be just fine.
Mother Natalie!
Lia! Pete! Everybody!
Damn it!
Cici...
Cess?!
Thank goodness! You're alive!
What are you doing here?!
It's my fault. I was such a fool.
What do you mean?!
Lord Luze was never going to let anyone
who knew of his replacement daughter live.
If I'd only realized sooner!
It's not your fault!
Can you walk? Where's everyone else?!
They killed them all.
You're the only one I didn't see dead.
Hey! We got a live one over here!
We'll flee out the back.
Where are they?!
I'm going after them!
Cess?!
Go on ahead! Call for help!
What are you talking about?!
Come with me!
They'll never stop chasing you
now that they've seen you!
I'll be fine.
Cess!
Go!
All my hard work to find that pawn,
only to have her broken so easily...
She was supposed to be at the mansion.
They never would've thought
she'd be at the orphanage.
This is all because Viscount Luze
tried to take matters into his own hands.
Nobles of his ilk are all the same.
What's this? A survivor?
What's your name?
Cici.
Oh.
A girl.
Come to think of it,
"Cici" was another nickname for Cecilia.
And you have perfect rosy eyes.
The mark of the Luze family.
I missed it because I took you for a boy.
I got the sense that girl
was hiding something.
Now I see it was you.
Cess went with that lord to protect me!
Do you hate Viscount Luze?
In that case,
what do you say I help you take revenge?
Revenge...?
If you do as we say,
we'll let you make that lowlife
suffer like you wouldn't believe.
Just do what your heart tells you.
Don't you hate him?
Don't you want to make him pay?
So just tear him down.
And this country with him.
You did it! That's my Cici!
Hey, quit it!
It's my fault. I was such a fool.
It's not your fault!
I'm going to play
the part of Miss Cecilia.
I don't...
want to hear anyone's voice anymore.
Oh, that reminds me. I've decided.
Decided what?
I told you. When to kill the O'Brian girl.
I thought we might as well make it
the day of Constance Grail's execution.
The day after tomorrow.
Oh.
Did you find out anything about Rufus?
It appears the real Rufus May
passed away ten years ago.
He was the youngest child
of less-than-wealthy nobles.
He came to the capital when his bad
conduct effectively got him disowned.
Ten years ago...
I see. So they replaced him back then.
Rest a little. I know you
haven't been sleeping.
I'm fine.
Whoops. Am I interrupting something?
No, that's all right.
Like I told you, Princess Alexandra
of Faris opposes war.
Wouldn't you like to see her
accede to the throne?
Your third princess has no lineage
or support worth mentioning.
Plus, isn't she a prisoner
in Faris right now?
I don't see what chance
she has of winning out.
But what if she got herself
a major backer?
What if King Ernst only said he was
going to talk trade with Melvina,
while really he went to Faris?
What?
But the king has no reason to go there.
He could always say he's paying
the king of Faris a get-well visit.
Only the fact that the captive
third princess invited him would matter.
I see. Word would spread on its own.
Word that Adelbide is allied
with the third princess.
Exactly. And just like that,
she'd have support.
But isn't the third princess locked up?
How is she going to invite the king?
Unless... the princess
in the tower is a double?
Hang on! You mean you're swaying
the whole nation with a bluff?!
It just goes to show how much
Faris fears your country.
Why didn't Crown Princess Cecilia
give me any answer at all?
You have a visitor.
Is that you, Brenda?
Well, um... What brings you here?
Look.
Kate and Mylene are
protesting my execution?!
Th-They aren't alone.
Your father, your ex-fiancé Neil Bronson,
and Viscount Hamsworth are all helping.
And the Earl of Ulster, of course.
His Lordship!
Tell me, Brenda, when am I to be executed?
Tomorrow, they say.
I see...
Listen, I'm... thinking
of accusing Pamela.
I'll testify to everything
she's ever done!
It's too little, too late, I know.
I've... I've been wanting
to tell you something all this time.
Thank you for saving me back then.
That wasn't me, Brenda. It was—
No, it was you.
Your sincerity saved me.
I'm not alone.
Everyone is fighting for me.
I'll never give up.
After all...
I'm sure that's what Scarlett would say.
Translation:
William Varteresian
Subtitle Timing:
Edgar Cruz
Subtitle Editing:
Riley Dalton
Quality Check:
SMR
Translation Check:
Sriram Gurunathan